<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="app_name">BookWorm</string>
	<string name="by">
		<b>By Charlie Collins</b>
		\n
	</string>
	
	<string name="aboutcontent">
		<i>Use BookWorm to keep track of books you have read, and you intend
			to read.
			Maintain a log of books that you can quickly view, sort, and
			rate.</i>
		&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		In the future this application will also be
		able to synchronize
		(import/export) with
		online book sources, and will include more features
		such as book reviews (in the works).\n
		&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
		For more
		information, and to comment or report
		issues,
		please visit &lt;a
		href="http://code.google.com/p/and-bookworm/"&gt;the
		BookWorm project
		site&lt;/a&gt;.
		&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	</string>
	
	<string name="scanningtips">    
    *If the scanner works but recognizes a product rather than a book, try looking for a different bar code. 
    Books often have multiple codes. The inside front cover may have another code that is different from the back.
    Especially for older paperback books, the inside cover code works more reliably.
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    *Make sure you are not scanning sticker that has been placed over the bar code by a retailer. Many retailers do this, 
    and the proprietary retailer codes will not scan.
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    *Some books just do not scan. Product codes that cannot be interpreted as ISBNs will not work. In those cases try a 
    web search for the title. It's still pretty quick, and it will likely work. 
    </string>
	
	<string name="aboutdetail">	
	
Changelog version 1.0.4: 
    &lt;br /&gt;
    *Enhancement - Add "enable debug logging" option in prefs (to try to help figure out other issues if they arise).
    &lt;br /&gt;
    *Enhancement - Add "Scanning Tips" menu option to no results found page.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    *Fix issue 10 - Force close after scan due to bar code format differences (EAN vs UPC, etc.). Should decode many more books now, and should not force close even when cannot decode.
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    *Fix issue 13 - Changing a book's title orphans the cover image. 
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;   

Changelog version 1.0.3: 
    &lt;br /&gt;
    *Fix issue 7 - Search web screen repeated results.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    *Fix issue 8 - Search web screen results not saved on orientation change.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    *Fix issue 9 - Search screen remember position in list.
    &lt;br /&gt;
    *Attempt Fix issue 10 - Force close after scan on some devices (this fix is not yet verified).
    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Changelog version 1.0.2: 
	&lt;br /&gt;
	*Fix issue 5 - reset cover image not persistent.
	&lt;br /&gt;
	*Fix issue 4 - make Splash skip the default.
	&lt;br /&gt; 
	*Additional small fixes, change detail menu logos, and add this about detail panel.
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

Please let me know if you come across any new issues, the project site issue tracker is where
	currently known issues and enhancement plans are logged. Thanks! 
	&lt;br /&gt;
	</string>
	<string name="books_list_empty">You don't have any books in your list yet. Use the
		Menu Add feature to add books.</string>
</resources>
